<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-03-20T02:40:56+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Basement</title><subtitle>Personal website of Abhirup Mukherjee</subtitle><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><entry><title type="html">Chekov’s gun and the use of perspectives: what makes Attack on Titan special</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/aot-why/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chekov’s gun and the use of perspectives: what makes Attack on Titan special" /><published>2023-03-19T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-03-19T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/AOT-why-see-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/aot-why/">&lt;p&gt;Hajime Isayama has pulled off something that I am sure all fiction lovers have dreamt of at some point: create a story that gives the impression that everything had been planned out since the very beginning. Complemented by some of the finest musical scores to appear out of the industry, Attack on Titan is a show that leaves you questioning your own moral compass at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/eren-face.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to sell Attack on Titan, I could just give the usual spiel about insane plot twists, thrilling backstories and engaging characters. While I &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; believe that Attack on Titan (AOT) is a show that embodies all these aspects to their fullest, such a pitch will probably not be that compelling for a random person. Instead, I will point out two specific (and somewhat meta) features of AOT that take the show into a class of its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;taking-chekovs-gun-to-the-extreme&quot;&gt;Taking Chekov’s gun to the extreme&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chekhov’s gun is a narrative principle that states that every element in a story must be necessary, and irrelevant elements should be removed. If a writer features a gun in a story, there must be a reason for it, such as it being fired sometime later in the plot. AOT takes this principle to its limit, such that almost every frame in the anime has some purpose which is realised by the viewers, sooner or later. This is a show which does not insult your intelligence in the slightest. No, seriously. Lose focus for a few seconds and you might miss a massive reveal!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/reiner-bert-face.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;powerful-use-of-perspective-in-story-telling&quot;&gt;Powerful use of perspective in story telling&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Several events in the show are presented repeatedly, but from different perspectives. The initial telling of the event is typically from a certain character’s or group’s point of view, and is designed to draw the viewers into sympathising with these character(s). A later-in-time telling of the same event from the opposing side then shatters the confidence of the viewer and makes them question their allegiance. This is used from time to time in the show to create a powerful effect where the viewer is able to empathise with all sides in the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/owl-eren.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the story is one of fantasy, the elements of fantasy only serve as metaphors for real world constructs, and the show has deep connections with the very world we live in, through mature and dark themes like racism, nationalism and imperialism. If nothing else, I leave you with the promise that AOT, as a show, is crafted out of utmost love and passion, and that is visible to anyone who watches the show.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="anime" /><category term="AOT" /><summary type="html">A few specific reasons why Attack on Titan redefined anime</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our work on an auxiliary model-based approach to the Mott MIT is now available on the arxiv.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2302.02328/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our work on an auxiliary model-based approach to the Mott MIT is now available on the arxiv." /><published>2023-02-09T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-09T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/esiam</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2302.02328/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Kondo frustration via charge fluctuations: a route to Mott localisation   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;pub__authors&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Abhirup Mukherjee&lt;/b&gt;, N. S. Vidhyadhiraja, Arghya Taraphder, Siddhartha Lal&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Feb 5, 2023   &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2302.02328&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--primary&quot;&gt;2302.02328&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;some-background-on-dmft-and-the-mott-mit&quot;&gt;Some background on DMFT and the Mott MIT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This work is devoted towards obtaining Hamiltonian-based insight into the dynamical mean-field theory (DMFT) treatment for the half-filled Hubbard model on the Bethe lattice in infinite dimensions. Our work offers an effective auxiliary model Hamiltonian that incorporates the effects of a local interacting self-energy (as obtained from the self-consistent approach of DMFT), and provides insight on the associated Mott metal-insulator transition (MIT). We recall that the conduction bath (of the effective impurity model within DMFT) becomes correlated under the requirement of self-consistency. The numerical implementation of this process precludes a deeper understanding of the precise nature of the correlations present in the conduction bath, and its implications for the electron dynamics of the associated bulk lattice (Hubbard) model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/dmft.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;
“Dynamical mean-field theory (DMFT) of correlated-electron solids replaces the full lattice of atoms and electrons with a single impurity atom imagined to exist in a bath of electrons. The approximation captures the dynamics of electrons on a central atom (in orange) as it fluctuates among different atomic configurations, shown here as snapshots in time.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://physicstoday.scitation.org/doi/10.1063/1.1712502&quot;&gt;[Source]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;questions-addressed-by-us-in-the-present-work&quot;&gt;Questions addressed by us in the present work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This leads to the following questions that we address in our work:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What are the quantum fluctuations that destroy the metal at \(T=0\) and lead to the insulating phase?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Can we obtain a universal theory for the competing tendencies that give rise to these quantum fluctuations?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What leads to the coexistence of metallic and insulating phases within DMFT at \(T=0\), as indicated by the fact that the insulating solution is already present within the many-body spectrum of the metallic phase prior to the transition?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is it possible to obtain a low-energy theory for the local gapless excitations precisely at the MIT, where the metal is on the brink of destruction?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-results-an-extended-anderson-impurity-model-and-its-qcp&quot;&gt;Main results: An extended Anderson impurity model and its QCP&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to model the interactions within the bath, we adopt an extended single impurity Anderson model (e-SIAM) as the effective auxiliary model for the Mott MIT. In addition to the usual impurity on-site repulsion U and the single-particle hybridisation V, we introduce&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;an additional on-site correlation (\(U_b\)) on the bath site with which the impurity couples, and&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;an antiferromagnetic Kondo coupling (\(J\)) between the impurity and the conduction bath.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These additions are then justified via a \(T=0\) renormalisation group (RG) analysis of the e-SIAM that reveals a quantum phase transition (QPT) at a critical value of the ratio (\(-U_b/J\)). The transition involves a change in the ground-state from a (Kondo) spin singlet to an unscreened local moment, indicating a Mott MIT in the bulk model associated with the chosen auxiliary model similar to DMFT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/esiam_bare.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;
We have extended the standard Anderson impurity model by incorporating an explicit Kondo coupling \(J\) and a local correlation \(U_b\) on the bath site coupled to the impurity. Such a model shows a local metal-insulator transition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-results-preformed-gap--excited-state-qpt&quot;&gt;Main results: Preformed gap = Excited state QPT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We use the fixed-point Hamiltonians obtained from the RG procedure to calculate quantifiers of the transition, e.g., various many-body correlation functions as well as measures of many-particle entanglement. These measures reveal that the transition occurs through a breakdown of the Kondo screening effect, owing to enhanced local pairing fluctuations in the bath proximate to the QPT. In the immediate neighbourhood of the transition, these pairing fluctuations also lead to the appearance of long-ranged correlations between the impurity and the conduction bath degrees of freedom, signalling critical behaviour. Remarkably, we find that the impurity QPT from metal to insulator is preceded by an excited state quantum phase transition (ESQPT): this involves the appearance of the local moment states in the many-body spectrum as excited states. This mechanism leads to a preformed (optical) gap in the impurity spectral function, as well as the coexistence region, in the phase diagram of the e-SIAM. This is consistent with the well-known phenomenology of DMFT.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;main-results-enhanced-pairing-fluctuations-and-non-fermi-liquid-excitations-at-the-mott-mit&quot;&gt;Main results: Enhanced pairing fluctuations and non-Fermi liquid excitations at the Mott MIT&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, the e-SIAM provides a minimal and universal local theory for describing Mott metal-insulator transition that arise from strong local correlations, and involves a competition between Kondo screening and its frustration from a locally correlated bath. The minimal model also offers detailed insights on the nature of the gapless excitations present at transition. We find that gapless non-Fermi liquid excitations arise from the ground state degeneracy at the transition, involving an orthogonality catastrophe and the vanishing of the quasiparticle residue of the local Fermi liquid. The non-Fermi liquid is characterised by anomalous power-law behaviour in the self-energy and various two-particle correlations, as well as a fractional entanglement entropy and magnetisation arising from a scattering phase shift of π/2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/coexistence-dmft.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; /&gt;
Qualitative structure of the finite temperature coexistence region of the \(J - U_b\) model. The dotted lines on the left and the right represent the spinodals where the insulating and metallic solutions become unstable, respectively. The solid red line represents the first-order line where the free energies and the partition functions of the two solutions become equal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusions-and-outlook&quot;&gt;Conclusions and outlook&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thus, our work offers a host of new results on multiple aspects of the auxiliary model approach to the Mott MIT. In general, the interplay of multiple correlations in the e-SIAM localisation from repulsion on the impurity site (\(U\)), delocalisation from spin and charge fluctuations (\(J\) and \(V\)), and pairing from local attractive correlations in the bath (\(U_b\)) - makes this a strong candidate for describing the emergence of a variety of novel phases of correlated quantum matter. Likely future investigations include, for instance, the effects of hole doping on the nature of the local quantum criticality observed by us, and especially whether critical pairing fluctuations can condense into a superconducting state of matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script type=&quot;text/javascript&quot; async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;https://cdn.mathjax.org/mathjax/latest/MathJax.js?config=TeX-MML-AM_CHTML&quot;&gt;
&lt;/script&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="preprint" /><category term="Updates" /><category term="impurity models" /><category term="Mott MIT" /><category term="auxiliary models" /><category term="Kondo effect" /><category term="quantum phase transition" /><summary type="html">In this work, we provide a Hamiltonian-based explanation of the phenomenology of DMFT, obtaining new insights on then MIT along the way.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The causality loop in Shingeki no Kyojin: Is there a paradox?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/aot-physics/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The causality loop in Shingeki no Kyojin: Is there a paradox?" /><published>2023-02-07T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-02-07T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/AOT-future</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/aot-physics/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The short answer is that there is no paradox: past, present and future all happen simultaneously there, so the question of causality doesn’t really arise. If you want to know what this means or how I came to that conclusion, read on.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Modern day masterpiece &lt;em&gt;Attack on Titan&lt;/em&gt; (AOT) is undoubtedly &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; most consistent television show I have ever experienced. The story is set in a post-apocalyptic world where mankind is on the brink of extinction and lives confined within walls in fear of huge humanoid creatures that are referred to as &lt;em&gt;titans&lt;/em&gt;. Because of the elements of fantasy, &lt;em&gt;the world of AOT operates by its own rules&lt;/em&gt; which the viewers learn gradually as the show progresses. Encouraged by the consistency and the incredible attention to detail ensured by the author, I have attempted to create a self-consistent set of physical laws for the AOT universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Needlesss to say, I will be spoiling all of Attack on Titan that has been aired until now (that is, upto the Final Season Part 2). You have been warned. There are no manga spoilers though.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;1-quantum-entanglement-connects-all-subjects-of-ymir&quot;&gt;1. Quantum entanglement connects all Subjects of Ymir&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/connected.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the central elements of fantasy in AOT is the fact that each and every subject of Ymir is connected to the Founding titan (and therefore to each other) through &lt;em&gt;the Paths&lt;/em&gt;. This connection is extremely non-local; it applies to all Eldians, no matter how far apart they are. This can be understood as &lt;em&gt;quantum entanglement&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the uninitiated, quantum entanglement is a weird phenomenon where two the properties of multiple objects remain correlated, even over very large distances. For example, we can have a device that produces a red ball and a blue ball and shoots them off randomly towards two volunteers \(V_1\) and \(V_2\). If volunteer \(V_1\) checks and finds that he has a red ball, he immediately knows that volunteer \(V_2\) has received a blue ball. The colour of the balls are thus correlated, and the balls can be said to be entangled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/all_subjects.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eren addressing all Subjects of Ymir using the Founding titan’s power can then be understood as a result of quantum entanglement between the Subjects and the Coordinate. Just as volunteer \(V_2\) can detect the colour of \(V_1\)’s ball simply by checking their own ball, the Subjects can know immediately what Eren’s brain is thinking by listening within their own brains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;2-the-paths-represent-wormholes-that-connect-all-eldians&quot;&gt;2. The Paths represent wormholes that connect all Eldians&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/ymir_eren_paths.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A wormhole (also known as Einstein-Rosen bridge) is, loosely speaking, a hypothetical tunnel that connects two distant points in space(-time). Wormholes emerge as solutions of Einsteins equations of general relativity that describe gravity. Recent pursuits by scientists like Leonard Susskind and Juan Maldacena have revealed that two entangled particles might be connected by a wormhole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/zeke_scream.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In light of the thesis presented in the previous point (that all subjects of Ymir are entangled with the Founding titan through the Paths), the Paths must be the corresponding wormholes that connect the entangled parties. For example, when Zeke screams and turns people who have consumed his spinal fluid into pure titans, he is actually channeling his intent and commands through the aforementioned wormhole. When Founder Ymir creates and heals titans, she sends the muscles and bones through these wormholes. That is why the bodies of titans appear almost instantaneously and out of thin air.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;3-time-flow-in-the-paths-is-orthogonal-to-that-in-the-physical-world&quot;&gt;3. Time flow in the Paths is orthogonal to that in the physical world&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/zeke_paths.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been stressed on numerous occasions by Zeke that time flows differently in the Paths. He says to Eren that “whatever happens in the Path, happens instantaneously”. This differential in time flow is also reflected in the fact even through the Founder Ymir expends untold number of years to create the flesh and bones of the titans, the body of the titan appears almost instantaneously in the physical world. This works out because the spacetime of the Paths realm lives in a dimension that is &lt;em&gt;orthogonal&lt;/em&gt; to the physical spacetime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Orthogonal dimensions are nothing special. On a chess board, horizontal and vertical movement are orthogonal, which means that you can shift a rook horizontally by as many squares as you want without needing to move it vertically. A similar geometry also exists between, say, the temporal directions of the physical and the Paths realms. This is shown in the image below. The time passage in the physical world is represented by the horizontal black line (“real time”), while time passage in the Paths real is represented by the vertical blue lines (“Paths time”).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/time_paths.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider the particular instant in real time when Gabi blows off Eren’s head (as represented by the red mark in the figure). One now has the freedom to move along “Paths time” by traversing the vertical blue axis that starts from the red mark, while keeping “real time” fixed at that that mark. This leads, for example, to the fact that Eren and Zeke spend many years in Paths time going through Grisha’s memories (longish green mark) while staying fixed at the red mark in “real time”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;4-superluminal-propagation-of-information&quot;&gt;4. Superluminal propagation of information&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/eren_address.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the physical world, there is a limit to how fast any information-carrying signal can travel. This limit is set by the speed of light in vacuum, which is roughly 3 followed by 8 zeroes, in the SI units. Neither light, nor therefore information, can be transmitted at arbitrarily high speeds. This is not true in the world of Attack on Titan, because the Paths make it possible to transmit information instantaneously over arbitrarily large distances. This was used by Eren to address all Subjects of Ymir living across the world. This superluminal propagation is again made possible because of the wormhole-like property of the Paths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-instantaneous-propagation--flattened-light-cones&quot;&gt;5. Instantaneous propagation = Flattened light cones&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/eren_address.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the physical world, there is a limit to how fast any information-carrying signal can travel. This limit is set by the speed of light in vacuum, which is roughly 3 followed by 8 zeroes, in the SI units. Neither light, nor therefore information, can be transmitted at arbitrarily high speeds. This is not true in the world of Attack on Titan, because the Paths make it possible to transmit information instantaneously over arbitrarily large distances. This was used by Eren to address all Subjects of Ymir living across the world. This superluminal propagation is again made possible because of the wormhole-like property of the Paths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;6-past-present-and-future-coexist&quot;&gt;6. Past, Present and Future coexist&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-physics/past_present.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the physical world, there is a limit to how fast any information-carrying signal can travel. This limit is set by the speed of light in vacuum, which is roughly 3 followed by 8 zeroes, in the SI units. Neither light, nor therefore information, can be transmitted at arbitrarily high speeds. This is however not true in the world of Attack on Titan, because the Paths make it possible to transmit information instantaneously over arbitrarily large distances. This was used by Eren to address all Subjects of Ymir living across the world. This superluminal propagation is again made possible because of the wormhole-like property of the Paths.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="anime" /><category term="AOT" /><summary type="html">Decoding the laws of physics in the world of Attack on Titan.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Turn VIFM into a Full-Fledged File Explorer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/vifm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Turn VIFM into a Full-Fledged File Explorer" /><published>2023-01-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/vifm</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/vifm/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/vifm/vifm&quot;&gt;Vifm&lt;/a&gt; is a terminal file manager for linux that relies heavily on vim-like keybindings. Overall it is quite fast and feature-full, making it a prominent choice among minimalist users. Below I mention some steps I have taken to make it more useful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of these require modifying only the VIFM config file. A good place to find/create such a file is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;~/.config/vifm/vifmrc&lt;/code&gt;. If this file already exists on your machine, create a backup of the file, because we will be editing it. Now delete all contents from the &lt;em&gt;original&lt;/em&gt; file (not the backup), and start with an empty &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;vifmrc&lt;/code&gt; file. If you do not have such a file at that location, create an empty file with that name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;coloured-filefolder-preview-and-suggestions&quot;&gt;Coloured file/folder preview and suggestions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VIFM, by default, has a left pane and a right pane. 
I have found that it is best to use the left pane as the standard file browser, and the right panel as a preview for the file/folder currently under the cursor.
That is enable by the following command:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; show file and directory preview in right pane
view!
&quot; preview text files using &quot;man&quot;
fileviewer {*.[1-8]},&amp;lt;text/troff&amp;gt; man ./%c | col -b
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This runs at startup and forces VIFM to use the right panel for preview.
The second command tells VIFM to use the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;man&lt;/code&gt; command for preview text files.
We can improve this by introducing multiple colours in the folder preview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; enable ls colors in folder preview
fileviewer */ ls --color=always
fileviewer .*/ ls --color=always
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two commands together instruct VIFM to use the shell command &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ls --color=always&lt;/code&gt; as a folder previewer. The resultant view is shown in the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/preview.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;enabling-suggestions&quot;&gt;Enabling suggestions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The functionality of the right panel can be improved by enabling suggestions in the right panel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; what to suggest on the right pane
set suggestoptions=normal,visual,view,otherpane,keys,marks,registers
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You might have set the keybinding &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;dd&lt;/code&gt; to delete a file, but you have forgotten whether it was &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;dd&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;dD&lt;/code&gt;.
The above setting makes it easy to recall these bindings: if you press ‘d’, the right panel will show all keybinding sequences that start with ‘d’, allowing the user to refresh their memory.
Besides keybindings, it also shows all the marks that you have defined.
For example, you might have forgotten whether you have marked your work folder to ‘w’ or ‘W’.
On pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;'&lt;/code&gt;, the right panel will show all the marks that you have defined in the vifmrc, making it easy to use the marks. This is shown in the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/suggestions.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;using-tabs-more-efficiently&quot;&gt;Using tabs more efficiently&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We often find it convenient to work simultaneously with multiple directories/views. This is where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;tabs&lt;/code&gt; become useful; you can have your work folder open in one tab and your downloads folder open in another tab, and copy files easily from one to the other. In order to make this process easy, insert the following lines in your vimrc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; create new tab
nnoremap &amp;lt;c-t&amp;gt; :tabnew&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;:view!&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;

&quot; switch to tab to the left
nnoremap H :tabprevious&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;:view!&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;

&quot; switch to tab to the left
nnoremap L :tabnext&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;:view!&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;

&quot; switch to tab to the left
nnoremap Q :q&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mappings, respectively, mean that you can use &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;CTRL+t&lt;/code&gt; to create a new tab, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;H&lt;/code&gt; to switch to the tab on the left, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;L&lt;/code&gt; to switch to the tab on the right, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Q&lt;/code&gt; to close to the current tab.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;trash-folder-for-safer-deletion&quot;&gt;Trash folder for safer deletion&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For safer delete operators, we enable the trash setting and set a trash folder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; enable trash and set trash folder
set trash
set trashdir=~/.local/share/Trash/files
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If the folder mentioned in the last setting does not exist, you have to create it. Once this is done, any file/folder that is deleted using the default &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;dd&lt;/code&gt; keybinding actually goes into the trash folder, and can be restored later. Permanent deletion can be performed through the more distant keybinding &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DD&lt;/code&gt;, to ensure that it does not happen accidentally. We can also remove the confirmation dialog that appears whenever we want to trash/delete a file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; remove confirmation before trash/delete
set confirm-=delete,permdelete
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;customise-the-statusline&quot;&gt;Customise the statusline&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bottom of the VIFM window shows a statusline where various pieces of information can be displayed. I prefer a simplistic status, where I show the filename at the left end (&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;%t&lt;/code&gt;), the current file size (&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;%20s&lt;/code&gt;) after that, then the file modification date (&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;%-30d&lt;/code&gt;), and finally the remaining storage on the file-system (&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;%a&lt;/code&gt;). The numbers represent the width of the blocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; set format of statusline
set statusline=&quot;%t %20s %= %-30d %a&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The format of the modification date can be set in the following way:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; set format of file modification time
set timefmt='%b %d, %Y @ %H:%M'
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The resultant statusline is shown in the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/statusline.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;navigation-using-marks&quot;&gt;Navigation using marks&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marks can be used as favourite folders to reach them quickly. They are defined in the following manner:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;mark h ~/
mark d ~/Downloads/
mark c ~/.config/
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inserting these lines into the vifmrc defines three marks corresponding to the three specified folders. Upon starting vifm, you can now press, say, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;'+d&lt;/code&gt; to change into the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Downloads&lt;/code&gt; folder. Same holds for the other marks. This provides a very fast method of accessing commonly used folders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;fuzzy-search-using-fzf&quot;&gt;Fuzzy search using fzf&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easier to search files using a fuzzy finder like &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;fzf&lt;/code&gt;. After installing the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;fzf&lt;/code&gt; binary (look up how you can do this in your specific distribution), fuzzy finding can be integrated into VIFM using the following lines:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; use fzf to fuzzy search and run file
command! FZFfind : set noquickview
                \| let $FZF_PICK = term('find ./* | fzf --height 10 2&amp;gt;/dev/tty')
                \| if $FZF_PICK != ''
                \|     execute 'goto' fnameescape($FZF_PICK)
                \| endif
nnoremap / :FZFfind&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above search is triggered by the keybinding &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/&lt;/code&gt;. It lists all files in the present directory and further down in the subdirectories and allows searching according to the provided prompt. The file that is selected (by pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Enter&lt;/code&gt;) is executed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;miscellaneous-options&quot;&gt;Miscellaneous options&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several settings which also help to be enabled. These are listed below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; useful options
set syscalls dotfiles wildmenu wildstyle=popup
set history=100 undolevels=100 followlinks norunexec
set ignorecase smartcase nohlsearch incsearch
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;syscalls&lt;/code&gt; instructs VIFM to use its internal methods for copy/paste operations rather than using utilities like &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cp&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;dotfiles&lt;/code&gt; makes the hidden files and folders visible in VIFM.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;wildmenu&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;wildstyle&lt;/code&gt; improve the way in which completion is shown for commands.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;history&lt;/code&gt; sets the maximum number of operations stored in history. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;undolevels&lt;/code&gt; sets the maximum number of actions that can be undone.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;followlinks&lt;/code&gt; means that clicking on a link directs you to the target. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;norunexec&lt;/code&gt; means clicking on executable files will not automatically execute them.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ignorecase&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;smartcase&lt;/code&gt; mean that search operations are case-insensitive unless there is at least one uppercase character.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;nohlsearch&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;incsearch&lt;/code&gt; mean that the search will be incremental and search results will not be selected before enter is pressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;keybindings-to-copy-file-name-etc&quot;&gt;Keybindings to copy file name, etc&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is very useful to set keybindings for common operations like copying the path of the parent directory, name of the current file under the cursor, and the full path of the current file. Through the commands below, these can be done with the keybindings &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;yd&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;yn&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;yp&lt;/code&gt; respectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; copy parent directory path to clipboard
nnoremap yd :!echo %d %i | xclip -i -r -selection 'clipboard' -f 
            \| xclip -i -r -selection 'primary'&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&quot; copy current file name to clipboard
nnoremap yn :!echo %c %i | xclip -i -r -selection 'clipboard' -f 
            \| xclip -i -r -selection 'primary'&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&quot; copy current file full path to clipboard
nnoremap yp :!echo %c:p %i | xclip -i -r -selection 'clipboard' -f 
            \| xclip -i -r -selection 'primary'&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;creating-new-files-and-folders&quot;&gt;Creating new files and folders&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first command below sets &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;t&lt;/code&gt; as the key to wait for a filename, and then creates an empty file with the name on pressing enter. The second command similarly does the same for a new folder, but with the key &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;M&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; mapping to create new blank file
nnoremap t :touch&amp;lt;space&amp;gt;

&quot; mapping to create new folder
nnoremap M :mkdir&amp;lt;space&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The directory creation is shown in the image below (notice the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;:mkdir&lt;/code&gt; at the bottom).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/mkdir.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;starting-a-shell-or-a-terminal&quot;&gt;Starting a shell or a terminal&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; mapping to open shell in pwd
nnoremap S :shell&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;

&quot; mapping to start terminal
nnoremap &amp;lt;a-t&amp;gt; :!$TERMINAL &amp;amp;&amp;lt;cr&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;S&lt;/code&gt; starts a shell in the current directory. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ALT+t&lt;/code&gt; spawns a new terminal by executing the environment variable &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;$TERMINAL&lt;/code&gt;. Since I use the simple terminal &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;st&lt;/code&gt;, mine is set to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;TERMINAL=st&lt;/code&gt; in my &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.bashrc&lt;/code&gt; file. A spawned terminal is shown in the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/terminal.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;keybindings-for-fast-rename&quot;&gt;Keybindings for fast rename&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two commands below allow renaming files quickly, by pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;a&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;A&lt;/code&gt;. The latter skips the extension and allows renaming only the basename, since that is what we typically do. The latter allows changing the entire filename, including the extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; rename without extension
nnoremap a cW 
&quot; rename with extension
nnoremap A cw
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We often have to select multiple files in a range, for copy or move operations. The two commands below make this easier: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SPACE&lt;/code&gt; selects one file and then moves the cursor down by one file, allowing us to press &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SPACE&lt;/code&gt; again immediately to select the next file. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;T&lt;/code&gt; does the same thing, but from bottom to top.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&quot; mapping to toggle select and move down
nnoremap &amp;lt;space&amp;gt; tj
&quot; mapping to move up and toggle select
nnoremap T kt
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An example of a selection is shown in the image below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/vifm/selection.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s all.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="unix" /><category term="software" /><category term="ncurses" /><summary type="html">Tips and tricks for making VIFM more powerful and versatile</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">All Foreshadowing and Easter Eggs in Attack on Titan: Season 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/aot-foreshadow/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="All Foreshadowing and Easter Eggs in Attack on Titan: Season 1" /><published>2023-01-08T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2023-01-08T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/AOT-foreshadowing1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/aot-foreshadow/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I will be spoiling the entirety of the anime&lt;/strong&gt;. You have been warned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AOT is particularly famous among its fans for the insane amount of foreshadowing it has.
Almost all plot twists and major events are hinted at in some way or the other, and seemingly innocent incidents and throwaway comments are found to be related to things that happen in the anime several years down the line (in real time). 
This is my attempt at creating a complete list of all subtle attempts made in the anime towards foreshadowing some major future event. 
The current post focuses on the events of Season 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-1&quot;&gt;Episode 1&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title of the first episode&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;em&gt;To you, 2000 years later&lt;/em&gt;. Self-explanatory.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren’s dream&lt;/strong&gt;: At the beginning of S1-EP1, Eren is shown to be having a “really long dream” where he sees certain future events like his mom getting eaten by a titan and Levi squad lying dead in the forest. Eren is not a shifter at this point, so it’s not clear how he was receiving memories. This is probably the only foreshadowing attempt which has not been explained yet in the show.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wallist preaching about the walls&lt;/strong&gt;: Just after the previous scene, a follower of the “Wall religion” is seen preaching to pedestrians about the walls. He says “The walls are the works of God! …”, hinting at the fact that the walls were made with the Founding Titan’s powers.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren’s reason for wanting to join the scout&lt;/strong&gt;: The entire interaction between Eren and Grisha in S1-EP1, on the question of joining the Survey Corps, is rather prophetic in hindsight. Firstly, Grisha asks Eren why he wants to “venture outside”, in reference to his own act of taking Faye beyond the walls of the Liberio internment zone. Secondly, part of Eren’s answer is that the sacrifices of those killed in the expeditions would be in vain if nobody followed in their footsteps. This evokes a particular reaction from Grisha, which we later realise is because he himself had similar reasons for undertaking Kruger’s mission.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/eren-scouts.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-2&quot;&gt;Episode 2&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren’s vows to kill them all&lt;/strong&gt;: “I’ll kill them all! I’ll wipe every one of them… off the face of the earth!” Enough said.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annie’s appearance&lt;/strong&gt;: A very young Annie is shown for the first time, taking rations as a refugee who has fled into Wall Rose.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reiner and Bertholdt’s appearance&lt;/strong&gt;: Young Reiner and Bertholdt are also shown within a few minutes of Annies’ appearance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/reiner-first.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-3&quot;&gt;Episode 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shadis skips recruits candidates who have already been through hell&lt;/strong&gt;: Eren and Mikasa’s trial-by-fire at Shiganshina is understable, but it is not clear why Shadis skips RAB and Ymir. RAB’s rite of passage, we later realise, is the Warrior training and the general discrimination in Marley. Ymir has also gone through a hell of her own, as seen in her flashback later.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on Reiner when Eren talks about the armoured titan&lt;/strong&gt;: During dinner, when Eren says that the armoured titan looked like a normal titan to him, the camera pans to Reiner.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steam is seen coming out of Eren’s injured head&lt;/strong&gt;: Eren’s titan healing ability kicking in.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bertholdt’s story about his village&lt;/strong&gt;: Bertholdt’s story about how titan’s attacked his village is later shown in Season 4 to be the same story that RAB heard from some villager when they first entered Wall Rose.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reiner wants to return to his homeland&lt;/strong&gt;: Reiner says that he only cares about returning to his “abandoned homeland,…,no matter what”. He is talking about returning to Liberio and to his family after completing the mission.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Grisha, today your son has become a soldier.”&lt;/strong&gt;: Shadis’ words to himself hints to some connection between Keith Shadis and Grisha Jaeger.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/shadis-grisha.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-4&quot;&gt;Episode 4&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annie points out the contradiction in the system where the best soldiers are sent farthest away from the titans.&lt;/strong&gt;: Annie, while practising martial arts with Eren, points out that the military system of their world is internally contradictory, because the candidates who are top of the class are encouraged to join the military police and stay within the inner walls, even though they should be best suited for fighting titans. This is probably intentionally enforced by the government so that the secret of the titans remains hidden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-5&quot;&gt;Episode 5&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The teacher’s comments  on titans&lt;/strong&gt;: During one of the classes for the trainees, the teacher makes a number of interesting comments. He says that the titan’s lack reproductive organs. The inference would then be that they have no need for reproduction, and some external party was sending them here. The teacher also says that most appear male, which might be because male Eldians were more likely to end up becoming restorationists or being generally impulsive enough to end up being prosecuted by Marley.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The final most important comment is that the titans’ only purpose in life appeared to be consuming humans, even though they can survive without that. This is of course because the titans are looking for a titan shifter, by consuming whom they can revert back to humans.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren is shown to release steam when he loses a leg in the battle for Trost&lt;/strong&gt;: Titan healing powers at play again.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-6&quot;&gt;Episode 6&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mikasa awakens her Ackermann powers&lt;/strong&gt;: When Eren calls for Mikasa to fight, her entire body and particularly her brain is shown to undergo a transformation, signalling the awakening of her Ackermann powers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/eren-scarf.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-8&quot;&gt;Episode 8&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reiner questions Connie what he knows about the “abnormal” titan&lt;/strong&gt;: When Connie is talking about the strange behaviour of Eren’s titan and that they can use its rampaging behaviour to escape the dire situation, Reiner asks Connie how much he “knows about the titan”. Reiner was curious because he realised that the titan was probably a shifter.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reiner and Annie opine that they should protect the “abnornal” titan&lt;/strong&gt;: They obviously want to figure out if that is a shifter.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-9&quot;&gt;Episode 9&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren’s words in the belly of Santa titan&lt;/strong&gt;: “I’ll annihilate you. Every single one of you. I’ll destroy you with my own hands.” Sounds suspicious again.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Their memories will show you how to use it!”&lt;/strong&gt;: Grish’s says this to Eren before injecting him with titan serum. He is referring to the fact that Eren will get the memories of the past inheritors, and those memories will show him how to transform.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“If you want to save Mikasa, Armin and everyone else, you have got to take control of this power.”&lt;/strong&gt;: This is another of Grisha’s statements to Eren. Very similar to what Kruger says to Grisha before being eaten by the latter.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RAB rush when they hear a titan transformation&lt;/strong&gt;: When Eren transforms to shield Mikasa and Armin from the canonball, RAB are the first to rush there.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-10&quot;&gt;Episode 10&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“If something beyond man appeared before us as a powerful foe, mankind will take up arms together in unity”&lt;/strong&gt;: Pixis describes an old legend to Eren atop Wall Rose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/pixis.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-13&quot;&gt;Episode 13&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annie is seen apologising to someone in her head, after the battle for Trost&lt;/strong&gt;: I guess she was thinking of Marco.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-15&quot;&gt;Episode 15&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Who do you think the enemy is?”&lt;/strong&gt;: Erwin’s words to Eren, when Sawney and Bean were killed. Prophetic words that come back throughout the series.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-16&quot;&gt;Episode 16&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Armin, while standing in line with Annie for their ODM gear inspection, is seen staring intently at Annie’s gear.&lt;/strong&gt;: Armin had notice that Annie was carrying Marco’s gear instead of her own.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-17&quot;&gt;Episode 17&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Avenge that reckless idiot”&lt;/strong&gt;: Armin’s trap for the female titan.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reiner pulls his hood back when fighting the female titan&lt;/strong&gt;: Armin had advised Reiner and Jean to keep their hoods pulled up all the way, because he felt the female would not kill anyone without knowing who they are. Despite that, Reiner pulls his hood back when attacking the female titan. We know the reason for that now: he wanted Annie to recognise him.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/levi.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-19&quot;&gt;Episode 19&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Levi’s thoughts about Eren&lt;/strong&gt;: In the forest of giant trees, Levi says the following about Eren: “He’s a true monster. And not because of his titan abilities. No matter how you try to hold him down. No matter what cage you lock him up in… Forcing his mind into submission is an impossible task.” Spot on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-21&quot;&gt;Episode 21&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren, while fighting the female titan, says “A-“, before the latter decapitates him.&lt;/strong&gt;: He recongnised the fighting stance of the female titan, and was going to say “Annie!”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-22&quot;&gt;Episode 22&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The female titan is seen crying, when Levi and Mikasa extract Eren from her and escape.&lt;/strong&gt;: Annie was crying because she would not be able to go home to her father yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;episode-23&quot;&gt;Episode 23&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Annie says “I don’t care if I’m swept along by the flow, as long as I’m still considered a human”.&lt;/strong&gt;: I believe Annie is saying that she does not mind becoming a warrior and killing Eldians if that helps her being recognised as an honourary Marley an and getting to live an honourable live with her father.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/aot-foreshadowing/annie.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;episode-25&quot;&gt;Episode 25&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eren says “I will destroy everything in the world. … I’m free.” near the end of his second fight with Annie.&lt;/strong&gt;: The first part is definitely foreshadowing the rumbling. The second part, “I’m free”, sheds light on Eren’s psyche, because it makes it clear that Eren’s idea of freedom involves destroying the barriers in his path.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s everything I could find in the first season.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="anime" /><category term="AOT" /><summary type="html">This is me trying to enumerate all foreshadowing attempts and hidden easter eggs in the modern day masterpiece Attack on Titan (Shingeki no Kyojin).</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Getting Yourself a Beautiful Website Using Jekyll</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Getting Yourself a Beautiful Website Using Jekyll" /><published>2022-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-05T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/creating-ghpages-website</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/">&lt;p&gt;I work in a theoretical physics &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.iiserkol.ac.in/~slal/&quot;&gt;research group&lt;/a&gt;, and we recently decided to create a new website for the group. Since I had already worked on two websites, I wanted to take this up. For the benefit of myself as well as the others who will come after me and might have to handle the website, I decided to document the entire process, in as much detail as possible. I believe there are too many general-purpose blog posts on creating Jekyll websites in the wild (see, for example, &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://programminghistorian.org/en/lessons/building-static-sites-with-jekyll-github-pages&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://opensource.com/article/17/4/getting-started-jekyll&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;), so this will instead be an elaborate wiki for a very specific use case. The website will have a home page that gives an overview of the research of the group, a dedicated page for the list of publications, a gallery for the present and past members of the group, a page for a more detailed exposition on the topics of our research, as well as other miscellaneous content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/octojekyll.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;ruby-gems-and-jekyll&quot;&gt;Ruby, gems and Jekyll&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ruby_(programming_language)&quot;&gt;Ruby&lt;/a&gt; is an interpreted, high-level programming language. Libraries in &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ruby&lt;/code&gt; are referred to as &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RubyGems&quot;&gt;RubyGems&lt;/a&gt; is a package manager for &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ruby&lt;/code&gt; that makes installing and maintaining &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt; easier. &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/rubygems/bundler&quot;&gt;Bundler&lt;/a&gt; is a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/code&gt; whose job is to create consistent environments for running &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ruby&lt;/code&gt;. It does this by managing the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt; that the application depends on. Given a list of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt;, it can automatically download and install those &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt;, as well as any other &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt; needed by the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt; that are listed, &lt;em&gt;all at the appropriate versions&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/jekyll.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator written in &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ruby&lt;/code&gt;. It is in fact a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gem&lt;/code&gt; that takes text written in your favorite markup language and uses layouts to create a static website. You can tweak the site’s look and feel, URLs, the data displayed on the page, and more. Such a website can then be hosted on any server. &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/github-pages/&quot;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt; is a free option, where you can host the website on GitHub’s &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;github.io&lt;/code&gt; domain or on a custom domain name of your choice. &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt; was developed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tom_Preston-Werner&quot;&gt;Tom Preston-Werner&lt;/a&gt;, GitHub’s co-founder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In summary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gems&lt;/code&gt; are libraries in the language Ruby, managed by the RubyGems package manager&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundler&lt;/code&gt; creates environments from specified libraries and their versions&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt; is a ruby library that  generates a static website from the provided content&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With these definitions out of the way, we can now start creating the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;starting-with-a-base-theme&quot;&gt;Starting with a base theme&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;choosing-a-jekyll-theme&quot;&gt;Choosing a Jekyll theme&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are innumerable Jekyll themes on Github. Each such theme consists of a set of templates, layouts, stylesheets and so on. They represent standalone complete websites, and you can add content to it as well modify the existing colors, designs and so on. We will use the famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mmistakes/minimal-mistakes&quot;&gt;Minimal Mistakes&lt;/a&gt; theme created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mmistakes&quot;&gt;Michael Rose&lt;/a&gt;. It has a modern and attractive style, and allows for sufficient customisation. The simplest way to use the theme is to create a copy of it, and then add content on top of it or make modifications wherever necessary. There are a couple of ways of creating a copy of the theme, and both these methods involve its &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mmistakes/minimal-mistakes&quot;&gt;GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt;. A GitHub repository is simply a cloud storage location for the contents of the theme. In order to create a copy of this theme, we can either &lt;em&gt;download&lt;/em&gt; the theme or &lt;em&gt;fork&lt;/em&gt; it. Downloading the repository simply downloads the files, while forking the repository creates a copy of the repository under our own GitHub account. Since we would have to ultimately create a repository anyway, it is more efficient to just fork the theme repository. &lt;em&gt;A fork is a copy of a repository. Forking a repository allows you to freely experiment with changes without affecting the original project&lt;/em&gt;. Once we fork the repository, the new forked repository becomes our base website which we can then tweak.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;forking-the-theme-repository&quot;&gt;Forking the theme repository&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the steps will be performed from the account of &lt;strong&gt;epqm&lt;/strong&gt;, my research group. To fork the repository, go to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mmistakes/minimal-mistakes&quot;&gt;Minimal Mistakes GitHub repository&lt;/a&gt; and click the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Fork&lt;/code&gt; button at the top right of the webpage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/fork.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fork button is encircled in the screenshot above. Alternatively, you can just go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mmistakes/minimal-mistakes/fork&quot;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;. Either way, you will end up on the page shown in the screenshot below. In order to finish creating the forked repository, you need to insert a name for the new repository, in the space provided under &lt;strong&gt;Repository name&lt;/strong&gt;. In order to act as a GitHub Pages website, the name of the repository has to be of the form &lt;code&gt;&lt;i&gt;username&lt;/i&gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, where &lt;em&gt;username&lt;/em&gt; has to be replaced with the name of the GitHub user account, which in this case is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;epqm&lt;/code&gt;. Choosing any other name will not allow the repository to be used as a website. Once a suitable name has been entered (a green tick should appear adjacent to the name), click the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Create fork&lt;/code&gt; button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/fork2.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;deploying-the-website&quot;&gt;Deploying the website&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository for containing our website has now been created, but the website itself is not active yet. In order to activate it, click on the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Settings&lt;/code&gt; button at the right end of the top menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/settings.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Inside the settings, click on the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Pages&lt;/code&gt; option in the left sidebar menu.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/pages.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are now in the GitHub Pages part of the settings for our repository. Within these settings, you will have to set the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/code&gt; by clicking on the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Branch&lt;/code&gt; menu and choosing the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;master&lt;/code&gt; branch. Branches are essentially views of a repository. If we so desire, the files in the repository can be kept in multiple states, each state representing a branch. Any of these branches can be used to deploy a website. By default, there is only one branch, which is called the &lt;em&gt;master&lt;/em&gt; branch. By selecting &lt;em&gt;master&lt;/em&gt; from the drop-down menu, we are choosing that branch as our website. After selecting &lt;em&gt;master&lt;/em&gt;, click on the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Save&lt;/code&gt; button adjacent to the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Branch&lt;/code&gt; menu to make the change permanent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/master.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website has now been deployed. After about 5 minutes, it should be possible to access the website at &lt;code&gt;https://&lt;i&gt;username&lt;/i&gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt;. We will have to modify the content in the repository in order to make this into a personalised website for our use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;summing-it-all-up&quot;&gt;Summing it all up&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We end this part by summarising the steps involved in creating and deploying the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The first step is to choose a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll theme&lt;/code&gt; on which to start creating the website.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The next step is to fork the GitHub repository of this theme. While forking, the name of the forked repository has to be of the form &lt;code&gt;&lt;i&gt;username&lt;/i&gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Once the repository is created, we need to go to the repository and click on &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Settings &amp;gt; Pages&lt;/code&gt;, and choose &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;master&lt;/code&gt; as the branch from which to deploy the website. This has to be confirmed by clicking on &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Save&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The repository looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/repo.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;git--markdown-cheatsheet&quot;&gt;Git &amp;amp; markdown cheatsheet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Going forward, we will be making use of git and markdown, so its necessary to get familiar with the relevant aspects of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-git&quot;&gt;What is git?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Git is a free version control system. It is used, at the very minimum, to track changes in software, allowing the possibility of rolling back changes, creating branches for working on multiple features simultaneously, and even removing specific changes among many others. We will need to know of a very small subset of the features of git for our purposes. A very basic workflow using git involves the following: (i) making some changes in a project, (ii) telling git to track the files, and hence note the changes made in the files, (iii) asking git to cement these changes by marking this state of the repository as a checkpoint, and (iv) uploading the changes to some cloud/online repository.
The second step is referred to as &lt;strong&gt;adding&lt;/strong&gt; the files. This is done using the command &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git add &amp;lt;file&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. The simplest way is to just add all the files in the project. That is done through &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git add .&lt;/code&gt;. The third step is referred to as &lt;strong&gt;committing&lt;/strong&gt; the changes, and each checkpoint is referred to as a &lt;strong&gt;commit&lt;/strong&gt;. Each commit is (preferably) accompanied by a &lt;strong&gt;commit message&lt;/strong&gt;. Commits are made using the command &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git commit -m &amp;lt;commit message&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. The fourth step is referred to as &lt;strong&gt;pushing&lt;/strong&gt; the commit, and is as simple as &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git push&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some other actions that we might find useful. Creating a local copy of an online repository (say, from GitHub) is referred to as &lt;strong&gt;cloning&lt;/strong&gt; the repository: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git clone &amp;lt;repository url&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;. Fetching the latest version of a cloned repository from the online source is referred to as &lt;strong&gt;pulling&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git pull&lt;/code&gt;. We will also often end up in the following scenario: after committing some changes, we realise that we have forgotten to add some small edit to the commit. This is rectified by making all the changes to the project, adding all the files, and then &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ammending&lt;/code&gt; the previous commit while keeping the commit message unchanged: &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git commit --ammend --no-edit&lt;/code&gt;. The option &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;--ammend&lt;/code&gt; means we are rectifying the previous commit, while the option &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;--no-edit&lt;/code&gt; means we are keeping the previous commit message unchanged. Note that you need to add the files before running the new commit command. If you had also pushed the previous incomplete commit, you need to add a &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;-f&lt;/code&gt; flag when you now push the new amended commit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;summary-of-git-commands&quot;&gt;Summary of git commands&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a summary of the git commands that are relevant to us. Each command is a concrete example.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cloning a repository:
    &lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git clone https://github.com/epqm/epqm.github.io
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pulling the latest version of repository:
    &lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git pull
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adding and committing the changed files, then push online:
    &lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git add file1 file2 # EITHER add specific files
git add . # OR add all files, just to be sure
git commit -m &quot;modified this and this&quot; # commit the changes
git push # push changes online
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Workflow for rectifying the latest commit:
    &lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;git add file1 file 2
git commit -m &quot;this is a commit&quot;
git push
# realise you forgot to add a file to the commit
git add file1 file2 file3 # add the remaining file
git commit --ammend --no-edit # make the ammending commit
git push -f # force push the new commit to replace the old one
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;what-is-markdown&quot;&gt;What is markdown?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Markdown is a markup language: it allows us to create a formatted and structured document by using certain predefined symbols. The markdown file itself is just a plain text file, but it can be converted to other formats like pdf, html, docx, odt and others using software like pandoc. For example, if you write &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;# This is heading&lt;/code&gt; in a text file and pass this text file through a markdown-to-latex parser, that line will be replaced by &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;\section{This is a heading}&lt;/code&gt;. This is an example to illustrate what I meant when I said that markdown allows us to add formatting by using only a few symbols. Jekyll allows us to create our webpages in markdown. This means that we can write our posts in markdown, and Jekyll will convert that to html.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;summary-of-markdown-rules&quot;&gt;Summary of markdown rules&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following is a list of the markdown rules that we will often use to format our documents. The version of markdown that is used by our theme is called Kramdown. Kramdown supports some extra features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create headers of decreasing levels by using increasing numbers of &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;#&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;# Heading 1
## Heading 2
###### Heading 6
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make text bold or italic by enclosing within &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;**&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Normal text, **bold text**, _italic text_
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Create unnumbered list using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;-&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt; - item 1
 - item 2
 - item 3
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Write programming code by enclosing within &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;`&lt;/code&gt; :&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;`a += 1`
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insert a horizontal rule using three dashes:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;---
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insert a hyperlink using the syntax &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;[text](link)&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;[link to repo](https://github.com/epqm/epqm.github.io)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Insert a local image using the syntax &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;![title for image](path_to_image)&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;![this is an image](/assets/images/jekyll/edit-final.svg)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;modifying-the-website&quot;&gt;Modifying the website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modifying the website requires &lt;em&gt;pushing&lt;/em&gt; changes to the GitHub repository. Whenever we commit and push a change to the repository, GitHub will recompile the repository and update the website with the changes. There are two broad ways of pushing changes to the repository.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;using-githubs-web-interface-&quot;&gt;Using GitHub’s web interface ✘&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first way is to use the browser interface of GitHub. By opening the repository in your browser, you can edit any file and immediately commit the changes, and this will also update the website. To demonstrate this, we will update the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;README.md&lt;/code&gt; file. The REAME file is present to provide information regarding the repository. It is only displayed in the GitHub repository web interface, and is not displayed on the website. For example, the current README provides information on the Minimal Mistakes theme, because that is the repository from which we forked our repository. In order to update this file, click on the file name in the list of files.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/readme1.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;
This displays the contents of the file in the browser. In order to start editing the file, click on the edit icon &lt;i class=&quot;fas fa-pen&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;:
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/edit_icon.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;
This opens the file in the editor of GitHub. We can now update the contents of the README by deleting all the existing content and replacing it with something relevant and simple for the time being. The final form looks something like this:
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/edit-md.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;
To save the changes, we need to &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;commit&lt;/code&gt; them. This can be done by supplying a commit message in the box provided just under &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Commit changes&lt;/code&gt; near the bottom of the page, and then clicking on &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Commit changes&lt;/code&gt;.
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/edit-final.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have now added our first commit to the repository. Even though this does not affect the website (because the README is not displayed there), this exercise demonstrates how we can modify any file within the repository.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are, however, two issues with this approach:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can edit only a single file in each commit. You &lt;em&gt;cannot&lt;/em&gt; edit multiple files and then combine all those changes into a single commit.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You cannot preview the edit before you commit them. The only way to find out how the website will be affected by your edit is to check the website &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; you have committed the edits.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;working-with-a-local-copy-&quot;&gt;Working with a local copy ✔&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The more superior approach is to clone the repository (create a local clone in your machine), make changes in your local copy, commit those changes and then push the commits to the GitHub repository. This allows us to make multiple changes within a single commit. We can also preview the changes we have made, by building the repository using &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt;. While it is true that this requires us to setup &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt; in our local machines, it is only a one-time effort, and is not too tricky. This subsection is a bit long, so we summarise the steps here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#install-git-on-your-machine-and-download-the-repository&quot;&gt;Install git on your machine and download the repository&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#install-ruby-and-relevant-gems&quot;&gt;Install Ruby and relevant gems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#make-required-changes-to-files&quot;&gt;Make required changes to files&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#build-website-locally-using-jekyll-to-preview-changes&quot;&gt;Build website locally using Jekyll to preview changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#commit-and-push-changes-to-upstream-when-satisfied-with-changes&quot;&gt;Commit and push changes to upstream when satisfied with changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will now elaborate on each of these steps. Note that steps 1 and 2 are preparatory steps and need to be performed only once per website. They are performed only for setting up the environment. Steps 3-5 constitute the workflow that we follow in order to make regular changes to our website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;creating-a-local-environment&quot;&gt;Creating a local environment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;install-git-on-your-machine-and-download-the-repository&quot;&gt;Install git on your machine and download the repository&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The basics of git has been summarised in the &lt;a href=&quot;#git--markdown-cheatsheet&quot;&gt;relevant section&lt;/a&gt;. We start by discussing how to install it. On a Linux machine, run one of the following commands in the terminal, depending on the particular distribution you are using:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo pacman -S git # Arch-based distributions
$ sudo apt install git # Debian-based distributions
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are using macOS, run the following command in the terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ brew install git
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are using Windows, go &lt;a href=&quot;https://git-scm.com/download/win&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and click on the link that says &lt;strong&gt;64-bit Git for Windows Setup&lt;/strong&gt;. This will download the git installer for windows. Once the download has finished, click on the installer and go through all the steps, choosing the default option whenever you are prompted to make a choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we have installed git, we need to be able to run git commands. &lt;em&gt;Note that all commands must be run within the folder of the project&lt;/em&gt;. On Linux or macOS, you can just open a terminal in the folder of the project and run git commands in that folder. For example, in order to pull the latest version of a research project, we first change into that folder (using cd) and then run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;git pull&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ( ~ ) 
$ ( ~ ) cd &quot;/home/historia/storage/work/local MIT&quot;
$ ( local MIT ) git pull
Already up to date.
$ ( local MIT )
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On a Windows machine, we need to change into the folder of the project, right click inside the folder to reveal the drop-down menu, and select &lt;strong&gt;Git Bash Here&lt;/strong&gt; from the menu. This starts a terminal in the folder, where we can now run the same git commands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having installed git on your machine, the next step is to provide some details regarding the user account and authentication. Run the following commands in a terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ git config --global user.name &amp;lt;username&amp;gt;
$ git config --global user.email &amp;lt;email id&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;email id&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; are replaced with the username and email-id of your GitHub account. In order to push changes to the GitHub repository, one more step is necessary. In order to authenticate yourself, you need to generate a pair of public-private SSH keys, and add the public key to GitHub. To generate the key, run the following in a terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ssh-keygen -t ed25519 -C &quot;&amp;lt;email id&amp;gt;&quot;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After running this command, you might be presented with a number of prompts. Press enter at all of them. The final output should display, among other things, the location of the public key. For example, a typical output on Linux reads&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ ssh-keygen -t ed25519 -C &quot;historia@gmail.com&quot;
Generating public/private ed25519 key pair.
Enter file in which to save the key (/home/historia/.ssh/id_ed25519):
Enter passphrase (empty for no passphrase):
Enter same passphrase again:
Your identification has been saved in /home/historia/.ssh/id_ed25519
Your public key has been saved in /home/historia/.ssh/id_ed25519.pub
The key fingerprint is:
SHA256:0w4qTixw3jGOsNObS/5SN2/vkCAA5sjuXp8mjVH7Tek historia@gmail.com
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As is apparent, the second line gives the location of the public key. In order to add the public key to GitHub, follow the steps laid out in &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.github.com/en/authentication/connecting-to-github-with-ssh/adding-a-new-ssh-key-to-your-github-account&quot;&gt;this GitHub docs page&lt;/a&gt;. There is one final step before we are done with setting up git. Whenever we want to push changes for the first time from our local repository to a GitHub repository, we need to specify the branch to which we want to push. In order to avoid doing this for every repository, we run&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ git config --global --add --bool push.autoSetupRemote true
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This informs git that any push action will happen between branches of the same name between the local and remote repositories. This concludes setting up git.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next step is to download the repository. The repository has a url, which can be obtained by opening the GitHub repository in the browser and looking at the navigation bar. For this example, we assume that this url is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;https://github.com/epqm/epqm.github.io&lt;/code&gt;. Copy this url from the browser, and run the following command in either the Linux/macOS terminal or in the Git Bash terminal on Windows:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ git clone https://github.com/epqm/epqm.github.io
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This will download the repository to your machine, into its own folder. By looking at the list of folders, you should be able to tell the name of the folder the repository was downloaded into. Assuming the name of the folder is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;epqm.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, we move into this folder by running &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ cd epqm.github.io
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;install-ruby-and-relevant-gems&quot;&gt;Install Ruby and relevant gems&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next step is to install Ruby and its gems. This is required in order to be able to compile the website locally and see what the website actually looks after the changes we made, before we commit and push the changes. &lt;em&gt;Note also that Ruby2.7 is the version that works best with Jekyll, so that is the version we will install&lt;/em&gt;. To install Ruby on a Linux machine, run one of the following commands, depending on your distribution:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo pacman -S ruby2.7 # Arch-based distributions
$ sudo apt install ruby2.7 # Debian-based distributions
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On macOS, run the following command:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ brew install ruby@2.7
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These commands need not be run within the repository folder. On Windows, you will need to first go to &lt;a href=&quot;https://rubyinstaller.org/downloads/&quot;&gt;this download page&lt;/a&gt; and click on the link that says &lt;strong&gt;Ruby 2.7.6-1 (x64)&lt;/strong&gt;. This downloads the Windows installer for the appropriate Ruby version. Once downloaded, click on the installer and go through the steps to install it, choosing the default option whenever asked to make a choice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now that we have installed Ruby 2.7, we have to get into gems. As mentioned before, RubyGems is the library-manager for ruby. It is used to install and remove Ruby libraries, which are also referred to as gems (hence the name RubyGems). The first step is to update RubyGems, and this is done through the commad:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ sudo gem-2.7 update --system # on Linux
$ sudo gem update --system # on macOS
$ gem update --system # on Windows
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This commands must be run in a Linux/macOS/Windows terminal. The Windows terminal can be accessed from the drop down menu that appears by holding down Shift and then clicking the right mouse button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having updated RubyGems, we now need to install the specific gems that are necessary for our website. The list of the necessary gems along with their versions is already provided in the repository in the form of Gemfile(s) which can be read by a gem named bundler. &lt;strong&gt;Bundler&lt;/strong&gt; makes it easy to install a specific set of gems. Note that the following two commands have to be run &lt;em&gt;inside&lt;/em&gt; the folder of the repository. You can either use your graphical file explorer to navigate into this folder and open a terminal there, or you can just &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/code&gt; into the folder from a terminal that was opened elsewhere. At any rate, ensure you are in a terminal and inside the repository folder. Then, run the following two commands:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ bundle config set --local path 'vendor/bundle' # set the location for installing gems
$ bundle-2.7 install # install the required gems 
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first command sets the location where the gems will be installed. The second command installs the required gems, into the location specified earlier. As mentioned before, the part after the ‘#’ acts as a comment which is ignored by the terminal and which has been provided just for your information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;broad-workflow-for-making-changes&quot;&gt;Broad workflow for making changes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;make-required-changes-to-files&quot;&gt;Make required changes to files&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just to demonstrate the workflow of making changes to the website, previewing it and pushing the changes, we will make a simple edit. Open the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_pages/about.md&lt;/code&gt; file in a text editor. There should be some text between two &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;---&lt;/code&gt; at the top of the page - do not edit that. Instead, remove all the text &lt;em&gt;below&lt;/em&gt; the bottom &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;---&lt;/code&gt;, and replace it with something else, like “Welcome to EPQM!”. Save the changes in the text editor and close it. The below images show the state of the file before and after the edit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/file-edit.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;build-website-locally-using-jekyll-to-preview-changes&quot;&gt;Build website locally using Jekyll to preview changes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having made some changes, it is time to compile the website using jekyll to preview the changes. In order to compile the website, &lt;em&gt;make sure that you are just inside the repository folder, and not inside anny of the subfolders within the repository&lt;/em&gt;. Having ensured this, start a terminal in the folder and run the following command:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ bundle-2.7 exec jekyll serve -lIw
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An explanation of this command is due. The first part &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle-2.7 exec&lt;/code&gt; means that we will be running the later part of the command inside the environment created by the gems listed in the Gemfile. This ensures that the correct versions of the libraries are used. The latter part &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt; instructs jekyll to compile the website and make it available to be viewed. You can view the website by opening the browser and going to the url &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000/&lt;/a&gt;. The final part &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;-lIw&lt;/code&gt; is a set of options that we have passed to jekyll.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The option &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;w&lt;/code&gt; stands for watch; it makes sure that if we keep this command running, jekyll automatically recompiles the website whenever we make and save any changes.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The option &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;l&lt;/code&gt; stands for livereload; it refreshes the browser whenever we make and save any changes, in order to reflect the modified website.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The option &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;I&lt;/code&gt; means incremental build; it allows faster compiling of the website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To see the effect our change in the about.md file, open the browser and go to &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/&quot;&gt;http://localhost:4000/&lt;/a&gt;. This will show the home page of the website. At the right end of the top bar, click on the &lt;strong&gt;About&lt;/strong&gt; tab, and this opens the about page of the website. In this page, we should be able to see the message we typed in earlier in the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;about.md&lt;/code&gt; file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/jekyll/about.svg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;commit-and-push-changes-to-upstream-when-satisfied-with-changes&quot;&gt;Commit and push changes to upstream when satisfied with changes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once we are happy with the changes, we need to commit and push them to GitHub, so that they are reflected on the actual website that can be viewed at &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;https://&amp;lt;username&amp;gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt;, which for us is &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;https://epqm.github.io/&lt;/code&gt;. As discussed above, the final steps are adding the files, committing the change and then pushing the changes to GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;$ git add .
$ git commit -m &quot;modified about&quot;
$ git push
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;important-point-about-editing-_configyml&quot;&gt;Important point about editing _config.yml&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As mentioned in the &lt;a href=&quot;#build-website-locally-using-jekyll-to-preview-changes&quot;&gt;Jekyll subsection&lt;/a&gt;, whenever we edit and save a file within the repository, the change is immediately reflected in the browser, as long as the Jekyll process is running in the background. This is true for editing all files except the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file at the root of the repository. Whenever you edit that file, the effect of this edit is not immediately visible. You need to stop the currently-running Jekyll process (by pressing &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;CTRL+c&lt;/code&gt; in the terminal) and start a new Jekyll build process (using exactly the same command as before). If you now refresh the browser tab, the change will be visible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;directory-structure-of-repository&quot;&gt;Directory structure of repository&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we need to get an idea of what the various folders and files in the repository mean. If you open the repository in any file manager, you should see the following items. Each listed item is followed by a very brief description. For more details, please check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/structure/&quot;&gt;appropriate page on the official website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;assets/&lt;/strong&gt;: This folder is used to store various binary files like images and video that we might want to show on the website&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.bundle/&lt;/strong&gt;: This folder is created by bundler to store files that it uses, for example configuration files.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_data/&lt;/strong&gt;: As the name suggests, this is the folder where you can store data files, like your list of publications or the names of books you have read. This data can be accessed using the &lt;em&gt;liquid&lt;/em&gt; variable &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;{{ site.data.&amp;lt;filename&amp;gt; }}&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.git/&lt;/strong&gt;: This folder is created by git and is used by git to do all its work. This should not be touched under normal circumstances.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_pages/&lt;/strong&gt;: This folder is used to store all the pages of the website. By pages, I mean content that is more of the blog kind, as compared to notifications and timely posts. Any file of the correct syntax and file name placed in this folder will be interpreted by Jekyll to be a webpage and will be rendered accordingly into the website.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_posts/&lt;/strong&gt;: This folder stores all the posts of the website. While the pages can be used to represent timeless content like tutorials, essays and blogs, &lt;em&gt;posts&lt;/em&gt; usually report notifications, updates and other timely content.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_site/&lt;/strong&gt;: This is where the final rendered website is created and stored, by Jekyll. GitHub pages looks into this folder and displays its content as the website. We don’t need to touch this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;vendor/&lt;/strong&gt;: This is the folder that we had provided to bundler as the location for installing the gems. As such, this is where you can find all the installed gems for this repository. We don’t need to touch this either.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;_config.yml&lt;/strong&gt;: This file can be used to define a large number of configuration settings for the website, including the title and description, color theme, social media links, website logo. We need to go through this file carefully and set appropriate values for the fields. Also note that while modifications to all other files will automatically be reflected in the browser if Jekyll has been run with the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;-lIw&lt;/code&gt; flags, modifications to the &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_config.yml&lt;/code&gt; file will not be automatically reflected; after saving the changes, you would need to restart the Jekyll process and then refresh the webpages.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gemfile&lt;/strong&gt;: This file is used to codify which gems (along with approximate versions) are required by the repository to function properly. It is used by bundler to create the required environment for compiling the website.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gemfile.lock&lt;/strong&gt;: This file additionally specifies exactly which versions of the gems mentioned in the Gemfile actually work. This exact version in Gemfile.lock is in contrast to the approximate versioning provided in the Gemfile. We should not need to touch this file.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.gitignore&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a file used by git; whichever file/path we list in this file will not be tracked (backed up or version-controlled) by git. For example, the vendor folder should be included in this file because we do not want to backup the installed gems - we can always install them anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;index.html&lt;/strong&gt;: This is the home page of the website.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.jekyll-metadata&lt;/strong&gt;: This helps Jekyll keep track of which files have not been modified since the site was last built, and which files will need to be regenerated on the next build. It is only created when using incremental regeneration. This file will not be included in the generated site.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;README.md&lt;/strong&gt;: This file is not rendered by Jekyll; it is instead rendered on the GitHub repository front page, and can be used to furnish information there.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;getting-started---basic-settings&quot;&gt;Getting started - Basic settings&lt;/h2&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="technology" /><category term="guide" /><summary type="html">Use the power of markdown to design a static website. Host it for free on GitHub ![](/assets/images/jekyll/octojekyll.png)</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our work on the multichannel Kondo problem is now available on the arxiv.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2205.00790/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our work on the multichannel Kondo problem is now available on the arxiv." /><published>2022-07-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-07-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/mckondo</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2205.00790/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Frustration shapes multi-channel Kondo physics: a star graph perspective   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;pub__authors&quot;&gt;Siddhartha Patra, &lt;b&gt;Abhirup Mukherjee&lt;/b&gt;, Anirban Mukherjee, N. S. Vidhyadhiraja, A. Taraphder, Siddhartha Lal&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
May 2, 2022   &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2205.00790&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--primary&quot;&gt;2205.0079&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We study the overscreened multi-channel Kondo (MCK) model using the recently developed unitary renormalization group (URG) technique. Our results display the importance of ground state degeneracy in explaining various important properties like the breakdown of screening and the presence of local non-Fermi liquids. The impurity susceptibility of the intermediate coupling fixed point Hamiltonian in the zero-bandwidth (or star graph) limit shows a power-law divergence at low temperature, signalling its critical nature. Despite the absence of inter-channel coupling in the MCK fixed point Hamiltonian, the study of mutual information between any two channels shows non-zero correlation between them. A spectral flow analysis of the star graph reveals that the degenerate ground state manifold possesses topological quantum numbers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The low energy effective Hamiltonian obtained upon adding a finite non-zero conduction bath dispersion to the star graph Hamiltonian for both the two and three-channel cases displays the presence of local non-Fermi liquids arising from inter-channel quantum fluctuations. Discontinuous behaviour is observed in several measures of ground state entanglement, signalling the underlying orthogonality catastrophe associated with the degenerate ground state manifold. We extend our results to underscreened and perfectly screened MCK models through duality arguments. A study of channel anisotropy under renormalisation flow reveals a series of quantum phase transitions due to the change in ground state degeneracy. Our work thus presents a template for the study of how a degenerate ground state manifold arising from symmetry and duality properties in a multichannel quantum impurity model can lead to novel multicritical phases at intermediate coupling.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="preprint" /><category term="Updates" /><category term="Kondo models" /><category term="impurity models" /><category term="Kondo breakdown" /><category term="non-Fermi liquid" /><summary type="html">In this work, we elucidate the importance of ground-state degeneracy and frustration in determining the physics of the multichannel Kondo model.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Moments that Saved Anime</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/moments/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Moments that Saved Anime" /><published>2022-06-20T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-06-20T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Moments-That-Saved-Anime</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/moments/">&lt;p&gt;Anime refers to a specific form of media - hand-drawn or computer-generated animated shows that originate from Japan. Anime differ from western animation productions in various aspects - art style, themes, target audience, etc. Anime have a distinct 2D style that has a particular appeal and that sets it apart from computer generated animation. The themes explored in anime are often very serious, ranging from shows like &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30/Neon_Genesis_Evangelion&quot;&gt;Neon Genesis Evangelion&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/339/Serial_Experiments_Lain&quot;&gt;Serial Experiments Lain&lt;/a&gt; that focus on the human psyche and depression, to more modern shows like &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1535/Death_Note&quot;&gt;Death Note&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1575/Code_Geass__Hangyaku_no_Lelouch&quot;&gt;Code Geass&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/16498/Shingeki_no_Kyojin&quot;&gt;Attack on Titan&lt;/a&gt; that deal with topics like racism, genocide and the subjective nature of morality. Some very popular and mainstream anime include Dragon Ball, Pokémon and Naruto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some moments in various anime series that have become iconic over the years and that portray the depth, intrigue and beauty of storytelling in this form of media. I have restricted myself to one moment per show, for the sake of versatility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Needless to say, there will be huge spoilers. You have been warned.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;fruits-basket-2019-the-final&quot;&gt;Fruits Basket 2019: The Final&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Lets make footprints in the snow together.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/machi.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fruits Basket is a series that I hold very close to my heart, particularly for the drama and romance aspects. In the final season, it is clear that all the various characters are moving beyond their insecurities into the outside world, forging new relations. In the quest to lend meaning to his life, Yuki finds a kindred broken soul in &lt;strong&gt;Machi Kuragi&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;kaguya-sama-love-is-war&quot;&gt;Kaguya Sama: Love is War!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“A once-in-a-lifetime wish from me to you.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/stanford.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hunter-x-hunter&quot;&gt;Hunter x Hunter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Komugi, are you there?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/name.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;clannad-after-story&quot;&gt;Clannad After Story&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“It’s the one you chose and bought for me.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/ushio-father.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;steins-gate&quot;&gt;Steins Gate&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;_ “You are about to begin… the longest and most imporant … 3 weeks of your life”_&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/weeks.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;naruto-shippuden&quot;&gt;Naruto Shippuden&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I, Madara, declare you the strongest.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/predicted.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-geass-lelouch-of-the-rebellion-2&quot;&gt;Code Geass: Lelouch of the Rebellion 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“And that… Yes. is the Zero requiem.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/requiem.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;attack-on-titan-season-3-part-2&quot;&gt;Attack on Titan Season 3 Part 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I keep moving forward…“&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video style=&quot;width:100%;&quot; controls=&quot;&quot;&gt;
  &lt;source src=&quot;/assets/videos/kruger.mp4&quot; type=&quot;video/mp4&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/video&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="anime" /><category term="rankings" /><summary type="html">Anime refers to a specific form of media - hand-drawn or computer-generated animated shows that originate from Japan. Anime differ from western animation productions in various aspects - art style, themes, target audience, etc. Anime have a distinct 2D style that has a particular appeal and that sets it apart from computer generated animation. The themes explored in anime are often very serious, ranging from shows like Neon Genesis Evangelion and Serial Experiments Lain that focus on the human psyche and depression, to more modern shows like Death Note, Code Geass and Attack on Titan that deal with topics like racism, genocide and the subjective nature of morality. Some very popular and mainstream anime include Dragon Ball, Pokémon and Naruto.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My A-to-Z Anime Ratings: the best as well as the worst</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/myanimelist/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My A-to-Z Anime Ratings: the best as well as the worst" /><published>2022-06-10T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-06-10T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/My-Anime-Ratings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/myanimelist/">&lt;p&gt;Anime refers to a specific form of media - hand-drawn or computer-generated animated shows that originate from Japan. Anime differ from western animation productions in various aspects - art style, themes, target audience, etc. Anime have a distinct 2D style that has a particular appeal and that sets it apart from computer generated animation. The themes explored in anime are often very serious, ranging from shows like &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30/Neon_Genesis_Evangelion&quot;&gt;Neon Genesis Evangelion&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/339/Serial_Experiments_Lain&quot;&gt;Serial Experiments Lain&lt;/a&gt; that focus on the human psyche and depression, to more modern shows like &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1535/Death_Note&quot;&gt;Death Note&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1575/Code_Geass__Hangyaku_no_Lelouch&quot;&gt;Code Geass&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/16498/Shingeki_no_Kyojin&quot;&gt;Attack on Titan&lt;/a&gt; that deal with topics like racism, genocide and the subjective nature of morality. Some very popular and mainstream anime include Dragon Ball, Pokémon and Naruto.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/anime-ratings/Arima.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Arima Kousei, from Your Lie in April&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are my personal ratings of the anime that I have watched over the years. They are pulled from my &lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/profile/SearyBlue&quot;&gt;MAL profile&lt;/a&gt;. All ratings are out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10&lt;/strong&gt;: blasphemous&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9&lt;/strong&gt;: unwatchable&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8&lt;/strong&gt;: repulsive&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7&lt;/strong&gt;: boring&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6&lt;/strong&gt;: watchable&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5&lt;/strong&gt;: average&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4&lt;/strong&gt;: enjoyable&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3&lt;/strong&gt;: wonderful&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2&lt;/strong&gt;: outstanding&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1&lt;/strong&gt;: legendary&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Anime Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;My Rating&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;MAL Rating&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/7593/Kiss_x_Sis_TV&quot;&gt;Kiss x Sis (TV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.64&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/16498/Shingeki_no_Kyojin&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.53&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/18397/Shingeki_no_Kyojin_OVA&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin OVA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.86&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/25777/Shingeki_no_Kyojin_Season_2&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin Season 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.50&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38524/Shingeki_no_Kyojin_Season_3_Part_2&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3 Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.07&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/25781/Shingeki_no_Kyojin__Kuinaki_Sentaku&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin: Kuinaki Sentaku&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.41&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/36106/Shingeki_no_Kyojin__Lost_Girls&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin: Lost Girls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.80&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/40028/Shingeki_no_Kyojin__The_Final_Season&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin: The Final Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.84&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/48583/Shingeki_no_Kyojin__The_Final_Season_Part_2&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin: The Final Season Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.84&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/22147/Amagi_Brilliant_Park&quot;&gt;Amagi Brilliant Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.48&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/31988/Hibike_Euphonium_2&quot;&gt;Hibike! Euphonium 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.30&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/5680/K-On&quot;&gt;K-On!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.85&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/7791/K-On&quot;&gt;K-On!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.17&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/43969/Kanojo_mo_Kanojo&quot;&gt;Kanojo mo Kanojo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.58&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32182/Mob_Psycho_100&quot;&gt;Mob Psycho 100&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.48&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37510/Mob_Psycho_100_II&quot;&gt;Mob Psycho 100 II&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.81&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30/Neon_Genesis_Evangelion&quot;&gt;Neon Genesis Evangelion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.34&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/2476/School_Days&quot;&gt;School Days&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5.55&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/2001/Tengen_Toppa_Gurren_Lagann&quot;&gt;Tengen Toppa Gurren Lagann&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.63&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/41457/86&quot;&gt;86&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.24&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/33486/Boku_no_Hero_Academia_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Boku no Hero Academia 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.16&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/4059/Clannad__Mou_Hitotsu_no_Sekai_Tomoyo-hen&quot;&gt;Clannad: Mou Hitotsu no Sekai, Tomoyo-hen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.95&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1365/Detective_Conan_Movie_06__The_Phantom_of_Baker_Street&quot;&gt;Detective Conan Movie 06: The Phantom of Baker Street&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.30&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1313/Digimon_Adventure_02&quot;&gt;Digimon Adventure 02&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38088/Digimon_Adventure__Last_Evolution_Kizuna&quot;&gt;Digimon Adventure: Last Evolution Kizuna&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.17&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32901/Eromanga-sensei&quot;&gt;Eromanga-sensei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.39&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/27989/Hibike_Euphonium&quot;&gt;Hibike! Euphonium&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.00&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/42897/Horimiya&quot;&gt;Horimiya&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.21&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/431/Howl_no_Ugoku_Shiro&quot;&gt;Howl no Ugoku Shiro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.66&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/40839/Kanojo_Okarishimasu&quot;&gt;Kanojo, Okarishimasu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.22&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/16662/Kaze_Tachinu&quot;&gt;Kaze Tachinu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.10&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/9656/Kimi_ni_Todoke_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Kimi ni Todoke 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.99&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/48926/Komi-san_wa_Comyushou_desu&quot;&gt;Komi-san wa, Comyushou desu.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.03&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/164/Mononoke_Hime&quot;&gt;Mononoke Hime&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.68&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/24227/Nisekoi_OVA&quot;&gt;Nisekoi OVA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.38&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30276/One_Punch_Man&quot;&gt;One Punch Man&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.51&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/28297/Ore_Monogatari&quot;&gt;Ore Monogatari!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.91&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/13759/Sakura-sou_no_Pet_na_Kanojo&quot;&gt;Sakura-sou no Pet na Kanojo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/33836/Seiren&quot;&gt;Seiren&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.29&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/42351/Senpai_ga_Uzai_Kouhai_no_Hanashi&quot;&gt;Senpai ga Uzai Kouhai no Hanashi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.68&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/anime-ratings/anime_shots/fujiwara.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Anime Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;My Rating&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;MAL Rating&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/48736/Sono_Bisque_Doll_wa_Koi_wo_Suru&quot;&gt;Sono Bisque Doll wa Koi wo Suru&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.36&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/48171/Summer_Ghost&quot;&gt;Summer Ghost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.89&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/34822/Tsuki_ga_Kirei&quot;&gt;Tsuki ga Kirei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.09&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/743/Umi_ga_Kikoeru&quot;&gt;Umi ga Kikoeru&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.55&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39617/Yakusoku_no_Neverland_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Yakusoku no Neverland 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;5.36&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/48569/86_Part_2&quot;&gt;86 Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.71&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/101/Air&quot;&gt;Air&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.28&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/47/Akira&quot;&gt;Akira&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.16&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/8676/Amagami_SS&quot;&gt;Amagami SS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.31&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/6547/Angel_Beats&quot;&gt;Angel Beats!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.08&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/11111/Another&quot;&gt;Another&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.49&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/24833/Ansatsu_Kyoushitsu&quot;&gt;Ansatsu Kyoushitsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.10&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30654/Ansatsu_Kyoushitsu_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Ansatsu Kyoushitsu 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.51&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39195/Beastars&quot;&gt;Beastars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.88&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/31043/Boku_dake_ga_Inai_Machi&quot;&gt;Boku dake ga Inai Machi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.32&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/31964/Boku_no_Hero_Academia&quot;&gt;Boku no Hero Academia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.93&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/36456/Boku_no_Hero_Academia_3rd_Season&quot;&gt;Boku no Hero Academia 3rd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.09&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39565/Boku_no_Hero_Academia_the_Movie_2__Heroes_Rising&quot;&gt;Boku no Hero Academia the Movie 2: Heroes:Rising&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.02&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/28999/Charlotte&quot;&gt;Charlotte&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.75&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/35849/Darling_in_the_FranXX&quot;&gt;Darling in the FranXX&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/2962/Digimon_Adventure_02_Movies&quot;&gt;Digimon Adventure 02 Movies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38691/Dr_Stone&quot;&gt;Dr. Stone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.30&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/813/Dragon_Ball_Z&quot;&gt;Dragon Ball Z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.15&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/226/Elfen_Lied&quot;&gt;Elfen Lied&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.50&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/121/Fullmetal_Alchemist&quot;&gt;Fullmetal Alchemist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.12&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/17895/Golden_Time&quot;&gt;Golden Time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.75&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/10793/Guilty_Crown&quot;&gt;Guilty Crown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.44&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/578/Hotaru_no_Haka&quot;&gt;Hotaru no Haka&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.50&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/10408/Hotarubi_no_Mori_e&quot;&gt;Hotarubi no Mori e&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.31&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/136/Hunter_x_Hunter&quot;&gt;Hunter x Hunter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.40&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1530/Kanon_2006&quot;&gt;Kanon (2006)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.97&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38993/Karakai_Jouzu_no_Takagi-san_2&quot;&gt;Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.09&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/49721/Karakai_Jouzu_no_Takagi-san_3&quot;&gt;Karakai Jouzu no Takagi-san 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.50&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38000/Kimetsu_no_Yaiba&quot;&gt;Kimetsu no Yaiba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.55&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/40456/Kimetsu_no_Yaiba_Movie__Mugen_Ressha-hen&quot;&gt;Kimetsu no Yaiba Movie: Mugen Ressha-hen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.66&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/49926/Kimetsu_no_Yaiba__Mugen_Ressha-hen&quot;&gt;Kimetsu no Yaiba: Mugen Ressha-hen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.39&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/47778/Kimetsu_no_Yaiba__Yuukaku-hen&quot;&gt;Kimetsu no Yaiba: Yuukaku-hen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.87&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/6045/Kimi_ni_Todoke&quot;&gt;Kimi ni Todoke&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.00&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30831/Kono_Subarashii_Sekai_ni_Shukufuku_wo&quot;&gt;Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku wo!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.12&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38040/Kono_Subarashii_Sekai_ni_Shukufuku_wo_Movie__Kurenai_Densetsu&quot;&gt;Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku wo! Movie: Kurenai Densetsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.47&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/anime-ratings/anime_shots/oreki.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Anime Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;My Rating&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;MAL Rating&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32380/Kono_Subarashii_Sekai_ni_Shukufuku_wo__Kono_Subarashii_Choker_ni_Shukufuku_wo&quot;&gt;Kono Subarashii Sekai ni Shukufuku wo!: Kono Subarashii Choker ni Shukufuku wo!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.85&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32949/Kuzu_no_Honkai&quot;&gt;Kuzu no Honkai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.18&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/18153/Kyoukai_no_Kanata&quot;&gt;Kyoukai no Kanata&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.74&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/33487/Masamune-kun_no_Revenge&quot;&gt;Masamune-kun no Revenge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.75&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39535/Mushoku_Tensei__Isekai_Ittara_Honki_Dasu&quot;&gt;Mushoku Tensei: Isekai Ittara Honki Dasu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.37&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/45576/Mushoku_Tensei__Isekai_Ittara_Honki_Dasu_Part_2&quot;&gt;Mushoku Tensei: Isekai Ittara Honki Dasu Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.74&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/20/Naruto&quot;&gt;Naruto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.97&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1735/Naruto__Shippuuden&quot;&gt;Naruto: Shippuuden&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.24&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32553/Nisekoi__OVA&quot;&gt;Nisekoi: OVA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.06&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/20507/Noragami&quot;&gt;Noragami&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.96&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30503/Noragami_Aragoto&quot;&gt;Noragami Aragoto&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.17&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/27775/Plastic_Memories&quot;&gt;Plastic Memories&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.92&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/13601/Psycho-Pass&quot;&gt;Psycho-Pass&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.35&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/4921/Ramayana__The_Legend_of_Prince_Rama&quot;&gt;Ramayana: The Legend of Prince Rama&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.18&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/42203/Re_Zero_kara_Hajimeru_Isekai_Seikatsu_2nd_Season_Part_2&quot;&gt;Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu 2nd Season Part 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.48&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30015/ReLIFE&quot;&gt;ReLIFE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.99&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37450/Seishun_Buta_Yarou_wa_Bunny_Girl_Senpai_no_Yume_wo_Minai&quot;&gt;Seishun Buta Yarou wa Bunny Girl Senpai no Yume wo Minai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.27&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/849/Suzumiya_Haruhi_no_Yuuutsu&quot;&gt;Suzumiya Haruhi no Yuuutsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.84&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/21647/Tamako_Love_Story&quot;&gt;Tamako Love Story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.93&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38826/Tenki_no_Ko&quot;&gt;Tenki no Ko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.31&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/27899/Tokyo_Ghoul_√A&quot;&gt;Tokyo Ghoul √A&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.03&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/36511/Tokyo_Ghoul_re&quot;&gt;Tokyo Ghoul:re&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.38&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37799/Tokyo_Ghoul_re_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Tokyo Ghoul:re 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;6.40&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/41389/Tonikaku_Kawaii&quot;&gt;Tonikaku Kawaii&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.92&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/4224/Toradora&quot;&gt;Toradora!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37521/Vinland_Saga&quot;&gt;Vinland Saga&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.73&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/14813/Yahari_Ore_no_Seishun_Love_Comedy_wa_Machigatteiru&quot;&gt;Yahari Ore no Seishun Love Comedy wa Machigatteiru.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.02&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39547/Yahari_Ore_no_Seishun_Love_Comedy_wa_Machigatteiru_Kan&quot;&gt;Yahari Ore no Seishun Love Comedy wa Machigatteiru. Kan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.38&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/23847/Yahari_Ore_no_Seishun_Love_Comedy_wa_Machigatteiru_Zoku&quot;&gt;Yahari Ore no Seishun Love Comedy wa Machigatteiru. Zoku&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.23&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/35507/Youkoso_Jitsuryoku_Shijou_Shugi_no_Kyoushitsu_e_TV&quot;&gt;Youkoso Jitsuryoku Shijou Shugi no Kyoushitsu e (TV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.86&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/9989/Ano_Hi_Mita_Hana_no_Namae_wo_Bokutachi_wa_Mada_Shiranai&quot;&gt;Ano Hi Mita Hana no Namae wo Bokutachi wa Mada Shiranai.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.33&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1690/Bokura_no&quot;&gt;Bokura no&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.63&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/35608/Chuunibyou_demo_Koi_ga_Shitai_Movie__Take_On_Me&quot;&gt;Chuunibyou demo Koi ga Shitai! Movie: Take On Me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.12&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/2167/Clannad&quot;&gt;Clannad&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.01&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38656/Darwins_Game&quot;&gt;Darwin’s Game&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.25&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1535/Death_Note&quot;&gt;Death Note&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.62&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/552/Digimon_Adventure&quot;&gt;Digimon Adventure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.77&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38680/Fruits_Basket_1st_Season&quot;&gt;Fruits Basket 1st Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.22&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/40417/Fruits_Basket_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Fruits Basket 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.57&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/5114/Fullmetal_Alchemist__Brotherhood&quot;&gt;Fullmetal Alchemist: Brotherhood&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.14&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/anime-ratings/anime_shots/ushio.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Anime Title&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;My Rating&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;MAL Rating&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/20583/Haikyuu&quot;&gt;Haikyuu!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.45&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/11061/Hunter_x_Hunter_2011&quot;&gt;Hunter x Hunter (2011)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.05&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/12189/Hyouka&quot;&gt;Hyouka&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.09&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37999/Kaguya-sama_wa_Kokurasetai__Tensai-tachi_no_Renai_Zunousen&quot;&gt;Kaguya-sama wa Kokurasetai: Tensai-tachi no Renai Zunousen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.40&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/32281/Kimi_no_Na_wa&quot;&gt;Kimi no Na wa.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.87&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/36098/Kimi_no_Suizou_wo_Tabetai&quot;&gt;Kimi no Suizou wo Tabetai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.57&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/22535/Kiseijuu__Sei_no_Kakuritsu&quot;&gt;Kiseijuu: Sei no Kakuritsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.35&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/28851/Koe_no_Katachi&quot;&gt;Koe no Katachi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.95&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/11887/Kokoro_Connect&quot;&gt;Kokoro Connect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.77&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/585/Mimi_wo_Sumaseba&quot;&gt;Mimi wo Sumaseba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.22&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/10620/Mirai_Nikki_TV&quot;&gt;Mirai Nikki (TV)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.45&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/18897/Nisekoi&quot;&gt;Nisekoi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.59&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/27787/Nisekoi_&quot;&gt;Nisekoi:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.36&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/19815/No_Game_No_Life&quot;&gt;No Game No Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.11&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/31240/Re_Zero_kara_Hajimeru_Isekai_Seikatsu&quot;&gt;Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.25&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/39587/Re_Zero_kara_Hajimeru_Isekai_Seikatsu_2nd_Season&quot;&gt;Re:Zero kara Hajimeru Isekai Seikatsu 2nd Season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.37&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38329/Seishun_Buta_Yarou_wa_Yumemiru_Shoujo_no_Yume_wo_Minai&quot;&gt;Seishun Buta Yarou wa Yumemiru Shoujo no Yume wo Minai&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.62&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/23273/Shigatsu_wa_Kimi_no_Uso&quot;&gt;Shigatsu wa Kimi no Uso&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.66&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/11577/Steins_Gate_Movie__Fuka_Ryouiki_no_Déjà_vu&quot;&gt;Steins;Gate Movie: Fuka Ryouiki no Déjà vu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.46&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/7311/Suzumiya_Haruhi_no_Shoushitsu&quot;&gt;Suzumiya Haruhi no Shoushitsu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.62&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/16870/The_Last__Naruto_the_Movie&quot;&gt;The Last: Naruto the Movie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.78&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/22319/Tokyo_Ghoul&quot;&gt;Tokyo Ghoul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.79&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/44931/Tonikaku_Kawaii__SNS&quot;&gt;Tonikaku Kawaii: SNS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.13&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/37779/Yakusoku_no_Neverland&quot;&gt;Yakusoku no Neverland&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.54&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/4181/Clannad__After_Story&quot;&gt;Clannad: After Story&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.94&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/1575/Code_Geass__Hangyaku_no_Lelouch&quot;&gt;Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.70&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/2904/Code_Geass__Hangyaku_no_Lelouch_R2&quot;&gt;Code Geass: Hangyaku no Lelouch R2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.91&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/42938/Fruits_Basket__The_Final&quot;&gt;Fruits Basket: The Final&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.03&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38883/Haikyuu_To_the_Top&quot;&gt;Haikyuu!! To the Top&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.36&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/43608/Kaguya-sama_wa_Kokurasetai__Ultra_Romantic&quot;&gt;Kaguya-sama wa Kokurasetai: Ultra Romantic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.16&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/40591/Kaguya-sama_wa_Kokurasetai_Tensai-tachi_no_Renai_Zunousen&quot;&gt;Kaguya-sama wa Kokurasetai? Tensai-tachi no Renai Zunousen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.65&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/38787/Senryuu_Shoujo&quot;&gt;Senryuu Shoujo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;7.40&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/35760/Shingeki_no_Kyojin_Season_3&quot;&gt;Shingeki no Kyojin Season 3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.62&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/9253/Steins_Gate&quot;&gt;Steins;Gate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9.08&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://myanimelist.net/anime/30484/Steins_Gate_0&quot;&gt;Steins;Gate 0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;8.52&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/anime-ratings/anime_shots/zeke.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; class=&quot;img__post&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="blog" /><category term="anime" /><category term="ratings" /><summary type="html">These are my personal ratings of the anime that I have watched over the years.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Our work on the single-channel Kondo problem has been published in Phys. Rev. B</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2111.10580/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our work on the single-channel Kondo problem has been published in Phys. Rev. B" /><published>2022-03-01T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-03-01T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/kondo-cloud-pub</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2111.10580/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Unveiling the Kondo cloud: unitary RG study of the Kondo model   &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;pub__authors&quot;&gt;Anirban Mukherjee, &lt;b&gt;Abhirup Mukherjee&lt;/b&gt;, N. S. Vidhyadhiraja, A. Taraphder, Siddhartha Lal&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Feb 2, 2022   &lt;a href=&quot;https://doi.org/10.1103/PhysRevB.105.085119&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--danger&quot;&gt;PRB 105, 085119&lt;/a&gt;   &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2111.10580&quot; class=&quot;btn btn--primary&quot;&gt;2111.1058&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We analyze the single-channel Kondo model using the recently developed unitary renormalization-group (URG) method and obtain a comprehensive understanding of the Kondo screening cloud. The fixed-point low-energy Hamiltonian enables the computation of a plethora of thermodynamic quantities (specific heat, susceptibility, Wilson ratio, etc.) as well as spectral functions, all of which are found to be in good agreement with known results. By integrating out the impurity, we obtain an effective Hamiltonian for the excitations of the electrons comprising the Kondo cloud. This is found to contain both k-space number diagonal (Fermi liquid) and off-diagonal four-fermion scattering terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our conclusions are reinforced by a URG study of the two-particle entanglement and many-body correlations among members of the Kondo cloud and impurity. The entanglement between the impurity and a cloud electron, as well as between any two cloud electrons, is found to increase under flow towards the singlet ground state at the strong-coupling fixed point. Both the number diagonal and off-diagonal correlations within the conduction cloud are also found to increase as the impurity is screened under the flow, and the latter are found to be responsible for the macroscopic entanglement of the Kondo-singlet ground state. The URG flow enables an analytic computation of the phase shifts suffered by the conduction electrons at the strong-coupling fixed point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This reveals an orthogonality catastrophe between the local-moment and strong-coupling ground states and is related to a change in the Luttinger volume of the conduction bath under the crossover to strong coupling. Our results offer fresh insight into the nature of the emergent many-particle entanglement within the Kondo cloud and pave the way for further investigations in more exotic contexts such as the fixed point of the overscreened multichannel Kondo problem.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Abhirup Mukherjee</name></author><category term="publication" /><category term="Updates" /><category term="Kondo model" /><category term="impurity models" /><summary type="html">In the work, we study the feedback effect of Kondo cloud screening on the conduction electrons, obtaining an effective Hamiltonian that describes its dynamics.</summary></entry></feed>